Sergey Lekontsev



Software Developer

Birth Date

06 October 1990

Ukraine

Lviv

Phone

+380989512646

WhatsApp/Telegram/Viber

+380950945777

LinkedIn

LEKSERG

Email

s lekontsev@outlook.com

Skills

Googling, HTML5, CSS3, JS, ES6+,

JQuery, Bootstrap, NodeJS Express,

NPM, Yarn, Command Line, GitHub,

RESTful API, Mongo DB, SQL, OAuth,

React JS, Router, Redux, Hooks

Languages:

Russian – Native Ukrainian – Native English – B1

Few words

Hi, I am 28 years old and I am looking for a company in which I can gain experience to improve skills and knowledge. I clearly realize the value of continuous growth. Having gained experience in other areas, I realized that the last 5 years have been lost and I definitely don't want to lose the following. Programming has always been magic for me, which is now at my fingertips.

Experience

Code examples: GitHub

Deployed projects: ToDo List

EJS Blog

<u>Simple Demo</u>

01/2019 – 04/2019 – React - The Complete Guide (Hooks, Router, Redux)

Udemy **Certificate** | **Course**

11/2018 – 01/2019 – The Complete 2019 Web Development Bootcamp

Udemy **Certificate** | **Course**

11/2015 – 05/2017 – Sales Manager | Computer store

09/2013 - 09/2014 - Sales Manager | Building materials store

Education

2008 – 2013 – Master's degree | Department of Economic Cybernetics

Stefanyk Precarpathian National University